[{"question": " buh-bye.  i just got us reservations at michelle\u0092s and tickets to the musicman to celebrate our first holiday season as a betroughed couple.", "answer": " betrothed\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " \u009abetrothed couple.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " hey! rachel and monica: hi!", "answer": " haaaa...  ... ahhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " pheebs?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " skull?", "answer": " oh, yeah, it's my mom's.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  oh my god!!", "answer": " no, no, no. it's not! it's not my mom. it belonged to mom. yeah, no, she used to put it out every christmas to remind us, that even though it's christmas, people still die. and, you can put candy in it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  licorice?", "answer": "  sure!  hey, i just found out, i get ben for the holidays this year.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " ohh! that's great!", "answer": " are you gonna dress up as santa?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " nope. i mean, i know susan does every year, but i think i wanna take this year to teach him all about hanukkah.", "answer": " and maybe i could teach ben about the christmas skull and how people die.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " you may need to use this year to teach ben about phoebe.", "answer": " hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  did you know he was in there?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " how long have we been home?", "answer": " about a half an hour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hey, you know what i was thinking? when we get married, are you gonna change your last name to bing?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " bing's weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  oh, hey, you guys!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey. guess what! my landlord just called and my apartment is gonna get ready soon, so i guess i'll be moving out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " ahh, phoebe, i'm gonna miss you!", "answer": " yes, you will be very sad. all right, well i gotta go tell rachel the good news.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " ohh! you guys gonna be living together again?", "answer": " yeah, why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " well, she's just so much fun with joey, i just assumed, she'd still be living with him.", "answer": " why do you think, she's having so much fun living with joey?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " no reason, except\u009ashe\u009atold\u009ame.", "answer": " really? so she said, she didn\u0092t wanna live with me anymore?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " no! no, she didn't say that. i-i-i think you should talk to monica now.", "answer": " phoebe, don't worry about it. i'm sure she wants to live with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " you're sure? you're absolutely sure?", "answer": " well, no. but, um, i bet she probably does.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! great, you\u0092re home! guess what phoebe got me for christmas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " drums?", "answer": "  no! drums!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " i'm sorry. but not that sorry, 'cause you don't have to live with it. um, we have a reservation under the name chandler bing.", "answer": " oh-kay, we'll have a table for you in about 45 minutes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " forty-five minutes? we have tickets to the musicman at 8:00.", "answer": " i'm sorry. christmas is a very busy time, sir.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " is this because of the burrito thing?", "answer": "  you need to give him money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " give him money? it was a joke!", "answer": " no, to get a table! places like are always shakin\u0092 you down. everybody wants to be paid off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " right, calm down, o'mally. i'll slip him some money.", "answer": " you've got to be smooth about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " of course, sir.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " how did it go?", "answer": " had the money in the wrong hand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " wooooooo, hehehe. hey, ahh, you don't feel like you're gonna throw up, do ya?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " well, i do, so let's...  so, ben, you uh, you know what holiday is coming up, don't ya?", "answer": " christmas.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yep, and you know what other holiday is coming up?", "answer": " christmas eve.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yes, but also  hanukkah! see, you're part jewish, and-and hanukkah is a jewish holiday.", "answer": " santa has reindeers that can fly!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " right, um, but, on hanukkah, hanukkah is a celebration of a miracle. see, years and years ago there were these people called the maccabees.", "answer": "  jingle bells, jingle bells...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  okay, that's right, yes, but on hanukkah, uh, we sing, uh  dreidel, dreidel, dreidel, i made you out of clay.", "answer": "  rudolph, the red-nosed reindeer...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  okay, it's not a contest.", "answer": " when is santa coming?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " well, how about this year, instead of santa, we have fun celebrating hanukkah?", "answer": " no santa? was i bad?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " no! oh, no-no-no. hey, you weren't bad, you've been very good, ben.", "answer": " santa's mad at me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " no, hey-hey, come on,  ben, santa is not mad at you, okay? hey, you're-you're his favorite little guy!", "answer": " so santa's coming?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " it's easy! just keep it casual! give him a kind word, shake his hand and give him the money!", "answer": " how do you know so much about this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i don't know.", "answer": " richard used to do it, didn't he?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " we'd be eating our soup right now.", "answer": " mustached bastard\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  okay, those people just left, come on! quick! give him the money and get their table!", "answer": "  excuse me...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  ha!", "answer": " so you like the drums! that's, that's great! y\u0092know, i was worried, that, you know, they would maybe an unbearable living situation. all right, okay, well, apparently not! so, yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey-hey, pheebs, check it out, we already learned a song.  ready? one, two, three, four...  rachel and joey: tequila!!", "answer": " that's fun.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " here you go.", "answer": " thank you gunther, put it there.  definitely not easier with coins.  thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " thank you.   hey pheebs!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " here.  now i only owe you $49.50.", "answer": " hey pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " if you wanna give joey a christmas present that disrupts the entire building, why not get him something a little bit more subtle, like a wrecking ball, or a vile of small pox to release in the hallway?", "answer": " it's not just the drum noise. every five minutes, joey throws his sticks in the air, and i have to hear, \"oh my eye! oh god, my eye!\" i mean, it is so annoying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yes, thank you. you see, this is how normal people are supposed to react to drums.", "answer": " phoebe, you got joey drums to annoy rachel, so she wouldn't wanna live there anymore?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " joey, y\u0092know that you could just not throw the sticks up in the air.", "answer": " what is rock 'n' roll about that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " oh wait, before you tell me what it is!  okay, what is it?", "answer": " it's a\u009atarantula!  oh! god! rachel, look, i'm sorry. what was i thinking giving joey this big, gross, scary spider in such a poorly constructed cage?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what are you talking about? i love them!  yeah, i had a tarantula when i was a kid. but it-it died, because my cat ate it. and then, then my cat died. but joey, isn't this cool?", "answer": " is it on me? i feel, i feel like it's on me! i got, hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh, isn't that adorable? joey is afraid of the tarantula.", "answer": "  ah, yeah, he's so adorable, god, he's just so much fun, joey is the best, i'm glad you're having so much fun here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " what? wait-wait a minute, what? phoebe, what's the matter?", "answer": " our apartment is ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " and that makes you angry because\u009a", "answer": " because you would rather live here with joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " where did you get that?", "answer": " monica and chandler said that you were having so much fun here. and apparently no amount of drums or tarantulas is gonna change that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " phoebe?", "answer": " hm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " did you get all this stuff for joey to try and drive me out of the apartment? honey, if you wanted to do that, you might as well just gotten him a fish, you know how fish freaked me out!", "answer": "  fish!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " it wouldn't have mattered anyway, phoebe, you and i are, are gonna live together, we're roommates; that's the deal.", "answer": " yes, but i wanted you to want to live with me, but okay, if you're having so much fun over here\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh, it's so much more fun with you.", "answer": " we did have fun, didn't we?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " we did!", "answer": " oh, anyway, they say, if we want, we can see it tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh, i would love to!", "answer": " yay, okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " great, all right, okay, and monica ask me to make the drumming stop.", "answer": "  um...  done!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hello, sir. you're here to return those pants?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " no, these are my pants.", "answer": " oh. okay! how can i help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well, uh, do you have a santa-outfit left?", "answer": " two days before christmas? sorry, man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i'm the holiday armadillo! i'm a friend of santa's and he sent me here to wish you  a merry christmas!", "answer": " what happened to santa, holiday armadillo?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  santa was unavailable so close to christmas.", "answer": " wow, come in, have a seat. you must be exhausted coming all the way from\u009atexas.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " texas?", "answer": " that's right, ben. i'm santa's representative for all the southern states. and mexico! but, santa sent me here to give you these presents, ben.  maybe the lady will help me with these presents.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " wow! thanks!", "answer": " you're welcome, ben. merry christmas, ooh, and happy hanukkah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " are you for hanukkah, too? because i'm part-jewish.", "answer": "  you are? me, too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " because armadillos also wandered in the desert?", "answer": "  you wanna wander in the hall?  ooh, hey ben, what if the holiday armadillo told you all about the festival of lights?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " cool!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " years and years ago there were these people called the maccabees...", "answer": "  ho, ho, ho! merry christmas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " what are you doing here, santa?", "answer": " well, i'm here to see my old buddy ben. what are you doing here, weird\u009aturtle-man?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i'm the holiday armadillo, your part-jewish friend. you sent me here to give ben some presents. remember?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " did you bring me any presents, santa?", "answer": " you bet i did, ben, put it there!   well, it would have worked this time, if his hands weren't so damn small!  ho, ho, ho!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  what are you doing?", "answer": " you called everyone and said you were having trouble finding a santa costume, so i borrowed one from a guy at work!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " thank you, but, but you gotta leave.", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " because, i'm finally getting him excited about hanukkah, and, and you're-you\u0092re wrecking it.", "answer": " but i didn't get to shape my belly like a bowl full of jelly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " i'm sorry, chandler but this, this is really important to", "answer": " fine, i'll give the suit back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " santa? really?", "answer": " yes, is that okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " did your dad ever dress up like santa?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " okay ben, santa has to go. say good-bye!", "answer": " no! why does he have to go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " because, if santa and the holiday\u009aarmadillo?  ...are ever in the same room for too long the universe will implode. merry christmas!", "answer": " no! why can't the armadillo leave? i want santa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " fine, i-i give up. santa, santa can stay.", "answer": " well, i'll stay, but only because i wanna hear about hanukkah. ben, will you sit here with santa and learn about hanukkah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " oh wow! look at this place!", "answer": " oh, this is terrible. oh, they\u0092ve made so many changes i can\u0092t even feel my grandmother\u0092s presence anymore\u0097ooh! new sconces!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  oh my god!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  okay, remember uh, remember how you told me that your grandmother put up that wall to make that into two bedrooms?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " and remember how you always said you were afraid the landlord would find out and then tear it down?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " do you really not know where i\u0092m going with this?  it left! it\u0092s one huge room!", "answer": " oh no!   oh! wow!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " see?", "answer": " well, i guess we\u0092ll just have to put the wall back up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " you can\u0092t, because of the new skylight!", "answer": " there\u0092s a skylight?!  wow!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " so what should we do? should we start looking for a new place?", "answer": "  y\u0092know i\u0092m-i\u0092m sensing that um, my grandmother would not be comfortable with that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " oh yeah? startin\u0092 to feel her again there are we?", "answer": " a little bit, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " pheebs is your grandmother maybe saying that you should live here alone?", "answer": " you heard her too?! you have the gift!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " phoebe, it\u0092s okay. i like living with joey.", "answer": " are you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " oh please, i hate packing, it\u0092s closer to work, and we do have fun. although, i\u0092m really gonna miss living with you.", "answer": " oh me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i know.  oh-oh, wait did you hear that-hear that? listen, i\u0092m gettin\u0092 something from your grandmother, she said that since you get to keep the one bedroom apartment you should give rachel the purple chair?", "answer": " no, i do not hear that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " \u009aand the miracle was that that little bit of oil that should\u0092ve just lasted just one day, burned for\u009a", "answer": "  eight whole days.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " that\u0092s right, and that\u0092s why we celebrate hanukkah today. the end.", "answer": " awesome!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " my favorite part was when superman flew all the jews out of egypt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": "  wow! it looks like the easter bunny\u0092s funeral in here.", "answer": " come on, come on, we\u0092re-we\u0092re-we\u0092re lighting the candles!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " i got it!", "answer": "  is it back in the cage?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " its back in cage!", "answer": " cage closed?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep10.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}]